我告诉卡尔  无论父母多有名
So I told Carl, nobody, no matter how famous their parents are...
都不准小孩爬恐龙
nobody is allowed to climb on the dinosaur.
可想而知  他是左耳进...
But, of course, this went right in one ear...
我最喜欢他认真起来的样子
I love how he cares so much about stuff.
要是眯起眼睛
If I squint,
我就能把他看成艾伦·艾尔达了
I can pretend he's Alan Alda.
好极了  又开始讲恐龙的故事了
Oh, good. Another dinosaur story.
恐龙怎么还没灭绝啊
When are those gonna become extinct?
如果我是一个会飞还会隐形的超级英雄
If I was a superhero who could fly and be invisible...
那就太棒了
... that would be the best.
瑞秋到底看上他哪一点
What does Rachel see in this guy?
我爱瑞秋
I love Rachel.
真希望她是我的老婆
I wish she was my wife.
谁在唱歌
Who's singing?
话说  你们小时候玩《欢乐时光》角色扮演
Hey, when you guys were kids and you played Happy Days...
都扮成什么  我总是扮里奇
who were you? I was always Richie.
我总是扮乔妮(里奇的妹妹)
I was always Joanie.
请问  "蛋洗盖勒家"
Question: Was "Egg the Gellers!"
是你们社区的作战口号吗
The war cry of your neighborhood?
是床垫大王
It's the Mattress King!
别看  亲爱的  赶快换台
Don't look, honey. Change the channel! Change the channel!
等一下  我想看  等我跟他离了婚
Wait! I wanna see this! After I divorce him...
那王国有一半都属于我
... half of that kingdom is gonna be mine!
床垫卖场愁云密布
Despair fills the mattress show room.
我的王国突然失去了皇后
My kingdom is suddenly without a queen.
我是如此沮丧
I'm so depressed...
我决定将价格
I'm going to slash...
砍到最低
my prices!
各位请看
Check it out!
豪华双人大床只要599
599 for a California king!
头部软垫双人床只要499
499 for a pillow-top queen set!
这价格一夜回到解放前
I'm going medieval on prices!
那个小人
What a wank!
他居然拿我们离婚的事做促销
I cannot believe he's using our divorce to sell mattresses!
就是啊  头部软垫双人床只要499
I know. At 499 for a pillow-top queen,
谁管你离不离婚
who cares about the divorce?
那些床垫肯定要卖疯了
Those babies will sell themselves!
还有  我为你感到震惊
And I'm appalled for you, by the way.
卖场最近  价格最低  我是床垫之王
I'm close! I'm cheap! I'm the King!
好的  爸  我们明晚见  再见
Okay, all right daddy. We'll see you tomorrow night. Okay, bye.
我们
"We"?
明晚要跟我爸吃饭  没问题吧
Are uh, having dinner with my dad tomorrow night. I hope that's okay.
糟糕  明天不方便
Oh, shoot! Tomorrow's not so good.
我应该会从帝国大厦掉下来
I'm supposed to fall off the Empire State Building...
落在没有座垫的脚踏车上  所以...
and land on a bicycle with no seat, so...
罗斯  我爸并不讨厌你
Ross, my father doesn't hate you.
拜托  他管我叫"油头"
Please. He refers to me as "Wet-Head. "
亲爱的  他喜欢给别人起外号
Honey, he calls everybody by a nickname.
好啦  就一顿饭
Look, I know, all right. Just one dinner.
就一晚上  为了我  求你了
Please one night. For me. Please?
我只是想让他像我一样爱你
I just want him to love you like I do.
好吧  也许不能像我一样
All right. Well, not exactly like I do.
不过如果你肯来
But if you do come to dinner...
我就穿你喜欢的黑色性感内衣好好爱你
I'll love you like I do in that black thing that you like.
我去
I'll go.
-好吧  -谢谢
- Fine. - Thank you.
你好  甘瑟
Hi, Gunther.
等着瞧
Yeah. We'll see.
大家好
Hey, you guys!
-你们猜怎么着  -怎么
- Guess what. - What?
-我有头路了  -好极了
- I got a gig! - Great!
所以我当不成演员  我从不会说"头路"
See, that's why I could never be an actor. Because I can't say "gig. "
我不会说"可颂"  天哪
I can't say "croissant. " Oh, my God!
-是什么角色  -不是角色
- What's the part? - It's not a part.
我要去函授学校教"连续剧演技"
I'm teaching Acting for Soap Operas down at the Learning Extension.
很棒啊
Come on! That's great!
我可以借此机会
It's, like, my chance to give something back...
回馈演艺界
to the acting community.
你应该知道
You know you're probably not
你不能跟学生上床
allowed to sleep with any of your students.
我知道
I know.
我不知道  莫妮卡
I don't know, Monica.
光是来这里就觉得很怪
It feels funny just being here.
在珍妮斯前夫的店买床垫
I mean, if you buy a bed from Janice's ex-husband
就像在背叛钱德勒
that's like betraying Chandler.
可这价格便宜啊
Not at these prices!
你好  在英国
Hi, you know, in England
这辆车应该放在店的另一边
this car would be on the other side of the store.
菲比  过来
Phoebe. Come here.
这就是我的新床垫
This is my new bed!
你一定要感受一下
You gotta feel this bad boy!
莫妮卡  我还是觉得怪怪的
Monica, it still feels so weird, you know?
钱德勒是你的朋友
Chandler's your friend.
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
买吧  朋友可以再交
All right, take this bed. You can make other friends.
晚上好
Good evening.
我是崔比安尼老师
I am Mr. Tribbiani.
我将教大家"连续剧演技"
And I'll be teaching Acting for Soap Operas.
好的
All right, now...
我扮演《我们的日子》中拉莫瑞医生的第一天
on my first day as Dr. Drake Ramoray on Days of Our Lives...
我学到演连续剧时很重要的一点
I learned one of the most important things in soap opera acting...
就是回应
is reacting.
这不是"重新表演"的意思
This does not mean acting again.
而是你没有台词  但可以听别人讲
It means you don't have a line, but someone else just did.
就像这样
And it goes something like this:
谢了  非常感谢
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
还有  先说明一点  如果想演连续剧
By the way, before I forget: To work in soap operas...
有些同学得让自己变漂亮些
some of you are gonna have to become much more attractive.
好了  继续往下讲
All right, moving right along...
昨晚课上得怎样
Oh, how was teaching last night?
很棒  我可以说
Oh, it's great! You get to say stuff like:
响铃并不代表下课   我说下课才能下课
"Hey, the bell doesn't dismiss you. I dismiss you. "
真好
Oh, nice.
你猜怎样  我要去《我的孩子们》试镜
Guess what? I got an audition for All My Children!
好极了
Oh, yeah!
是一个很棒的角色
Yes, it's this great part.
拳击手尼克
This boxer named Nick.
我超适合的  他跟我一模一样
And I'm so, so right for it. He's just like me.
除了他是拳击手
Except that he's a boxer...
有一个坏蛋双胞胎
... and has an evil twin.
请注意  床垫大王送货来了
Hear ye, hear ye! Delivery from the Mattress King!
-是盖勒小姐吗  -没错
- You Miss Geller? - Okay.
请签收
Sign here.
我有中间名吗
Do I have a middle name?
好吧  莫妮卡·费露拉·盖勒
All right. Monica "Felula" Geller.
抬到那个房间
It's that bedroom there.
莫妮卡从床垫大王买床吗
Monica bought a bed from the Mattress King?
求求你  不要告诉钱德勒
So please, please, please don't say anything to Chandler.
你要我骗钱德勒吗
You want me to lie to Chandler?
-有问题吗  -没有
- Is that a problem? - No.
拳击手尼克  露两手来瞧瞧
Oh, hey, "Nick the boxer. " Let's see what you got!
拳头举起来
All right, put them up. Come on.
你蛮有架势的嘛
Hey, you're pretty good at this.
我非学不可  我住在基督教青年会时
I had to learn. I was staying at the Y...
有些男生可不像基督徒
and some of the young men weren't acting Christian enough.
别闹了  喂
Hey, now! Hey!
我流血了  帅啊
And I'm bleeding. Okay, great.
我是素食者耶
Wow! And I'm a vegetarian!
对不起  来冰敷吧
All right, I'm sorry. We'll put some ice on it.
-把头仰起来  -好
- Put your head back. - All right.
-我看不到  -我来牵你
- I can't see. - I have you.
天哪
Oh, God!
盖勒小姐  要抬进哪个房间
Which bedroom do you want it in, Ms. Geller?
靠窗最整洁的那一间
It's the compulsively neat one by the window okay?
知道了
Gotcha.
爸爸
Hi, daddy!
被安排在这里吗
This is where they put us?
厨房挤不下了吗
What, there was no table available in the kitchen?
-你好啊  小宝贝  -记得罗斯吧
- Hello, baby. - You remember Ross.
格林医生  又见面了
Nice to see you again, Dr. Green.
那么
So...
图书馆还好吗
How's the library?
是博物馆
Museum.
-那图书馆呢  -没有图书馆
- What happened to the library? - There never was a library.
是有图书馆  只不过
I mean, there are libraries. It's just...
我没在图书馆做过事
that I've never worked at one.
知道这里的名菜是什么吗  龙虾
You know what's really good here? The lobster.
你们说我直接点三份如何
What do you say? Shall I just order three?
如果你当真如饥似渴
Yeah, if you're really hungry.
开玩笑  我开玩笑的
It was a joke. I made a joke.
爸爸  其实罗斯对龙虾过敏
Actually, daddy, Ross is allergic to lobster.
什么人会对龙虾过敏啊
What kind of person's allergic to lobster?
我猜只有图书管理员才会
I guess the kind of person that works in a library.
-不是...  -我知道  是博物馆
- It's not... - I know. It's a museum!
难道只有你可以开玩笑吗
Why? You're the only around here who can make a joke?
至少我的很好笑
At least mine was funny.
服务员
Waiter.
两份龙虾  一份菜单
We will have two lobsters and a menu.
格林医生  你的船好吗
So, Dr. Green, how's the old boat?
生锈了  你知道生锈船会怎样吗
They found rust. Do you know what rust does to a boat?
让船看起来像古董
Gives it a nice antique-y look?
锈是船的癌症  罗斯
Rust is boat cancer, Ross.
我真遗憾
Wow, I'm sorry.
我小时候就这样失去了一台脚踏车
When I was a kid, I lost a bike to that.
失陪一下
Excuse me for a moment, will you please?
我想在离开前问候下莱文家的人
I wanna say good night to the Levines before we go.
好的
Okay.
亲爱的  别这样  没那么糟
Honey, stop. It's not that bad.
你爸一定算错了  他只给了4%的小费
I think your dad must have added wrong. He only tipped like 4%.
是啊  我爸就是这样
Yeah. That's daddy.
我爸就是这样
"That's daddy"?
你不困扰吗  你就是服务生
Doesn't it bother you? You're a waitress.
我的确很困扰  罗斯
Yes, it bothers me, Ross.
如果他是咖啡馆的常客
But, you know. If he was a regular at the coffee house,
我会冲他的咖啡打喷嚏
I'd be serving him sneezers.
-所以呢  -所以  罗斯
- So? - So, Ross...
我跟他说过无数遍了  他不会改变的
I've bugged him about this a million times. He's not gonna change.
你真的会冲咖啡打喷嚏吗
Do you really serve people sneezers?
反正我不会
Well, I don't.
孩子们  可以走了吗
All right, kids. Ready?
格林医生  再次谢谢你
Thanks again, Dr. Green.
等一下
Wait...
我忘了拿收据
I think I forgot my receipt.
-不要拿了  -为什么
- You don't need that. - Why not?
复写纸很脏  沾到手指上
The carbon. It's messy. I mean, gets on your fingers
会引发
and causes the...
夜盲症
night blindness.
这是什么
What is this?
谁放了二十块  是谁
Who put a 20 down here? Huh?
对啊  应该是我
Oh, yeah, that would be me.
我有一个毛病
I have a problem.
我给的小费太高了  太高了
I tip way too much. Way too much.
-这是一种病  -没错
- It's a sickness, really. - Yeah, it is.
-我们得想个办法  -别说了
- We really really have to do something about that. - Excuse me.
你觉得我很小气吗
You think I'm cheap?
爸  他没有那个意思  真的
Oh daddy, he didn't mean anything by that. He really didn't.
我做的事都没有意义  真的
Nothing I do means anything. Really.
真好啊  我花两百块请客
This is nice. I pay $200 for dinner.
你只放了二十块就成了大少爷
You put down $20 and you come out looking like Mr. Big Shot.
你那么想当大少爷吗
You really want to be Mr. Big Shot?
这样吧
Here. I'll tell you what:
钱都给你出  大少爷
You pay the whole bill, Mr. Big Shot. All right?
"大少爷"总比"油头"好
Well, "Mr. Big Shot" is better than "Wet-Head. "
现在教你们几个小诀窍
Okay, some tricks of the trade.
我演戏一向哭不出来
Now, I've never been able to cry as an actor.
所以要是我得哭
So if I'm in a scene where I have to cry,
我就把裤子口袋挖一个洞
I cut a hole in my pocket...
放一把镊子在里面
take a pair of tweezers...
然后开始拔毛
and just start pulling.
如果我想表现
Okay, or let's say I wanna convey...
刚做了坏事的感觉
that I've just done something evil.
就秀出那个
That would be your basic
"眉毛鱼钩我喜欢"的表情
I've-got-a-fish-hook-in-my-eyebrow-and-I-like-it.
要是我听到一个坏消息
Let's say I've just gotten bad news.
只要心算232除以13就行了
Well, all I do there is try and divide 232 by 13.
就是这样
And that's how it's done.
今晚的课上得很愉快
Great soap opera acting tonight, everybody.
下课
Class dismissed.
-崔老师  -你好
- Hey, Mr. Trib. - Hey.
你猜怎么着  我要去试镜了
Guess what? I got an audition!
我的学生要试镜了  我好骄傲
One of my students got an audition. I'm so proud!
能不能请您指导我一下
I was wondering if you'd consider coaching me for it.
当然可以  是什么角色
You bet! What's the part?
那个角色很棒
Oh, it's great!
是《我的孩子们》里的拳击手尼克
It's a role on All My Children. Nick the boxer.
你非得这样吗  就不能睁只眼闭只眼吗
You had to do it, didn't you? You couldn't just leave it alone.
才4%
Four percent, okay?
就算菜里有虫  我也给的比他多
I tip more than that when there's a bug in my food.
罗斯  今晚吃饭是为了让你们好好相处
Ross, tonight was about the two of you getting along.
你快去找我的按摩治疗师好吗
Would you just see my chiropractor already?
是啊
Yeah,
一个没念过医科的治疗师
I'm gonna go to a doctor who went to medical school in a mini-mall.
菲比  你在干什么
Hey, Pheebs. What are you doing?
我快吓死了
I'm freaking out!
莫妮卡交待我办一件事  她不该这么做
Monica kind of trusted me with something and she shouldn't have!
我搬走一阵子了  所以我得问你
I haven't lived here in a while, so I have to ask you something.
莫妮卡依然会开卧室灯吗
Does Monica still turn the lights on in her bedroom?
没错
Yeah.
我死定了
I am so dead!
好了  最重要的是  罗斯
All right, look, here's the bottom line Ross.
赶紧补救还来得及
This is fixable if we act fast, okay?
我请他明天来吃早午餐  你可以示好
So I'll invite him to brunch tomorrow, and you can make nice.
亲爱的  我示好过了  没有用
Honey, I have tried to make nice. It doesn't work.
罗斯  我知道我爸很难相处
Okay, look, Ross, I realize my father is difficult.
所以你一定要比他大方
But that's why you have got to be the bigger man here.
亲爱的  我可以比他大方
Look, sweetie, I could be the bigger man.
我可以超级大方
I could be the biggest man.
就算我当一个巨人
I could be a big, huge, giant man,
事情也不会改变
it still wouldn't make a difference.
除非我可以把你爸拎起来说
Except I could pick your father up and say,
喜欢我吧  小医生
"Like me! Like me, tiny doctor!"
你就不能再试一次吗  罗斯
Can't you just try it one more time, Ross?
就当是为了我
For me? For me?
瑞秋  一顿早午餐解决不了问题
Rachel, one brunch is not gonna solve anything.
面对现实吧  我们合不来
You got face it, okay? We're never gonna get along.
你们非合得来不可
Okay, well, you are just going to have to, Okay?
我已经有一对
Because I've already got
无法共处一室的父母
a mother and father who cannot stay in the same room together, okay?
我不想再多你一个
I don't want to have a separate room for you too!
好的  好的
Okay, okay.
我去买百吉饼
I'll get the bagels.
这是什么
What's this?
很酷吧
Isn't it cool?
-这不是我买的床  -我知道
- This is not the bed I ordered. - I know!
你一定是赢了什么比赛了
You must have won, like, a contest or something.
菲比
Phoebe.
这辆车为什么在我的房里
Why is this car in my bedroom?
对不起  我没有注意
I'm sorry, okay? I wasn't looking...
店里不肯接受退货  因为你已经签收了
and the store said they won't take it back because you signed for it.
-我什么时候签收了  -当我是你的时候
- When did I sign for it? - When I was you.
这都怪乔伊不好  他没护住鼻子
You know what? It's all Joey's fault, because he left his nose open!
你今天抽大麻了吗
Did you make brownies today?
-有人在吗  -快
- Knock, knock! - Quick!
快脱衣服  他就不会注意到床了
Take off your dress. He won't notice the bed.
我要去吃寿司  有人要...
I'm going for sushi. Does anybody want... ?
有人错过了出口匝道吗
Somebody missed the off-ramp!
这是莫妮卡的床  怎么了
It's Monica's bed. What?
还行
Okay.
这是一辆赛车
It's a race car!
莫妮卡的床一直都是这张  你现在才发现吗
So this has always been Monica's bed. You were just noticed now?
你还真够自我中心的
How self-involved are you?
如果这不是新床
Okay, well, if this bed isn't new,
床垫上为什么有塑料膜
then how come there's plastic on the mattress?
我有时候会做恶梦
Sometimes I have bad dreams.
听着
Look...
我刚看到我死党的脑浆溅在拳击场上
I just saw my best friend's brain smeared across the canvas.
我不要跟他一样
It's not gonna be me.
我不要
Not me.
太精彩了  真是...
That was good. That was...
-有镊子吗  -没有
- Tweezers? - No.
-太精彩了  -谢谢
- That was really good. - Thanks.
您有什么建议吗
Any suggestions?
你叫他把拳击手演成同性恋
You told him to play the boxer gay?
我的原话应该是
Well, I might have said:
越基越好
"Super-gay. "
乔伊  你是他的老师  怎么能这样
Joey, you're this guy's teacher. I mean how could you do this?
莫妮卡  因为他演得太好了
Because, Monica, the guy's so good.
我真的很想拿到这个角色
And I really, really want this part.
要是你真的很想  那就没关系
Well, if you really, really want it, then it's okay.
-爸爸  -宝贝
- Hi, daddy. - Baby.
-罗斯  -格林医生  你好吗
- Ross. - Dr. Green, how are you?
谢谢你昨晚请客
Thanks for dinner last night.
谢谢你给我上了宝贵的一课
Thank you for teaching me a valuable lesson.
好帅的发型  你刚游完泳吗
Nice hair. What did you do, swim here?
够了  我受不了了
OK, that's it. I can't take it anymore.
怎么了  他对你有兴趣
What? He's interested in you.
他喜欢你的发型
He likes your hair.
-他只想知道你来之前在做什么  -得了吧
- He just wants to know how you got here. - Oh, please.
亲爱的  没用的  我要走了
Sweetie, it's hopeless. Okay? I'm just gonna go.
什么  罗斯
What? Ross...
-对不起  我实在...  -罗斯
- I'm sorry. It's just... - Ross?
你的脖子怎么了
What's with the neck?
他的脖子不舒服
He's got this thing.
我一直叫他去找我的按摩治疗师
I keep telling him to go to my chiropractor.
你还在找那位按摩治疗师吗
You're still going to that chiropractor?
他连乡下的医学院都考不上
That man couldn't get into med school in Ixtapa!
谢谢  我一直这么说
Thank you. That's what I keep saying.
抱歉  巴比医生是个很好的医生
Excuse me, Dr. Bobby happens to be an excellent doctor.
等一下  他叫巴比医生
Wait a minute. His name is Dr. Bobby?
-那是他的姓  -和他的名字
- That's his last name. - And his first name.
他叫巴比·巴比
He's Bobby Bobby?
是罗伯特·巴比
It's Robert Bobby.
恕我直言  他把我医好了
And excuse me, he helps me.
拜托  你问她是怎么医的
Please. Ask her how.
你哪里有毛病
What do you need help for?
我歪一边  有一条腿比较短
My alignment. I got one leg's shorter than the other.
-天哪  -跟她辩辩看
- Oh, my God. - Argue with that.
本来就是  我的右腿短了两寸
What! It's true! My right leg is two inches shorter!
得了  你只是没站直
Come on, you're just tilting!
-她的腿没有任何问题  -我知道
- Her legs are fine. - I know that.
那你为什么让她去找按摩治疗师
So why do you let her go to chiropractor for?
-不好意思  "让她去"  -我有什么办法
- I'm sorry, "Let her"? - What can I do?
她连承租保险的事都不听我的
She doesn't listen to me about renter's insurance either.
慢着  你没有承租保险吗
Wait a minute, you don't have renter's insurance?
没有
No.
你东西要是被偷了怎么办
Well what if somebody steals something?
你要用长短腿追贼吗
How will you run after the robber with one leg shorter than the other?
你要喝果汁吗
Would you like some juice?
-麻烦你  -不客气
- I'd love some juice. - Okay.
真顺利  你看到我们了吗
This is going so well! Did you see us? Did you see?
看到了  亲爱的  我就站在旁边
Yeah, honey. I was standing right there.
你怎么不提我那颗还没检查的痣
Why don't you just tell him about the mole I haven't got checked yet?
好主意
Excellent!
有一天  在你们的职业生涯里
There will come a time in each of your careers...
你们会有机会毁掉另一个电视演员
when you'll have a chance to screw over another soap opera actor.
前不久  我就有这样的机会
I had such an opportunity in the recent present.
很惭愧的是
And I'm ashamed to say that...
我也这么做了
I took it.
我建议另一位演员把角色
I advised a fellow actor to play a role...
演成同性恋
homosexually.
没错
Yeah.
我们参加同一个角色的试镜
We both auditioned for the part and...
结果是
as it turned out...
他们
they...
他们喜欢同性恋的演法  选了他
They liked the stupid gay thing and cast him.
现在
And now...
他拿到两年的合约  和他演对手戏的是
he's got a two-year contract opposite...
苏珊·露琪
Susan Lucci...
日间电视剧的女王
the first lady of daytime television.
而我呢
And me?
我被困在这里教别人演戏
Me, I'm stuck here teaching a bunch of people...
其中大多数都丑到根本上不了电视
most of whom are too ugly to even be on TV.
对不起...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry...
谢谢
Thank you.
-有什么需要吗  -有  你好
- May I help you? - Yes, hi.
我们通过电话
I talked to you on the phone.
我就是被硬塞了一张赛车床的人
I'm the lady who got stuck with the race car bed.
我跟你说过了  我无能为力
Look, it's like I told you. There's nothing I can do.
你已经签收了  "莫妮卡·费露拉·盖勒"
You signed for it. "Monica Felula Geller. "
行了  小丑兄  我们要见床垫大王
All right, jester man, we wanna see the King.
没有人可以见大王
Nobody sees the King.
好的  我就要找他说话
Okay. I'm talking to the King.
你不能到后面去
Hey, you can't go back there!
我  的  天
Oh, my God.
小姐  小心一点
Watch it, lady!
嘿  美女
Hey, good-looking.
好  我走
All right, I'll leave.
我的床好无聊
My bed's so boring.